Abdallah Bahaa

Software Engineer

King Faisal Street, Giza (+20) 1203588860 abdallah.bahaa2000@gmail.com Linkedin

SUMMARY

Computer science fresh graduate with a major in mobile and cloud computing. Experienced in Android mobile development. proficiency in Java, Kotlin, and Python, and certifications in mobile development and UI/UX design. possess strong problem–solving skills and experience working with cross–functional teams. Highly motivated and committed to continuous learning and growth.

EDUCATION

Canadian International College, New Cairo — Bachelor of Computer Science Mobile and Cloud Computing Major (2019-2023)

GPA: 3.53

EXPERIENCE

Ministry of Communication and Information Technology(MCIT) -

July 2022 - Aug. 2022

Training in Infrastructure, wireless and voice, Datacenter, Cybersecurity, Data science

Artronix Company - Mobile Developer Trainee

July 2021 - Aug. 2021

Android development training by building various projects, by java and kotlin

COURSES

Advanced Android Kotlin - Fwd & Udacity

User Interface and User Experience – Information Technology Institute

Machine Learning - CIC Faculty of Engineering

Python Programming - CIC

Web Design - CIC

Data Analysis With Python - CIC

MILITARY SERVICE: COMPLETED

Oct. 2023 - Dec, 2024

SKILLS

Hard Skills:

- Android Mobile Development
- Machine learning
- Java
- Kotlin
- Python
- C++
- Flask
- Laravel
- Microsoft Power Bi

Soft Skills:

- Leadership Experience
- Presentation
- Communication
- Team work
- Project management

PROJECT

Developer at imas2023 website

GRADUATION PROJECT

- **Project name:** Smart E-learning application
- Project description: Smart
 e-learning platform that
 connects students and
 companies through intelligent
 tools such as a recommendation
 system, content creation tools,
 and a CV creator.
- Grade: A+

LANGUAGES

- Native Arabic Speaker
- Advanced English